#Data obtained from https://opentdb.com !

question_data = [{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&quot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Animals","question":"A caterpillar has more muscles than humans do.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"History","question":"In World War ll, Great Britian used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to divert Hitler away from Normandy\/D-day landing.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as &quot;The Shape&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Politics","question":"The 2016 United States Presidential Election is the first time Hillary Clinton has run for President.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Computers","question":"&quot;HTML&quot; stands for Hypertext Markup Language.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The color orange is named after the fruit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Slovakia is a member of European Union-","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the video game development company Facepunch Studios in March 2009.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"The sum of any two odd integers is odd.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Bulls are attracted to the color red.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Sports","question":"In association football, or soccer, a corner kick is when the game restarts after someone scores a goal.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the Super Mario series, the character Pauline is a Princess like Princess Peach.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan \/ Case Closed!)","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"There is an island in Japan called \u014ckunoshima, A.K.A. &quot;Rabbit Island&quot;, so named because of it&#039;s huge population of rabbits.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Animals","question":"Rabbits can&#039;t vomit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Animals","question":"In 2016, the IUCN reclassified the status of Giant Pandas from endangered to vulnerable.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"A plant that has a life cycle for more than a year is known as an annual.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"No Game No Life first aired in 2014.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Mythology","question":"In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Books","question":"Stephen Chbosky wrote the book &#039;The Perks of Being A Wallflower&#039;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Computers","question":"Linux was first created as an alternative to Windows XP.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]